Guide to the UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Audio-Visual Materials 1987-1998
UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Audio-Visual Materials
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Audio-Visual Materials, 1987-1998
6000/026 AV
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE); UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs
2 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees.; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs--Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
Subjects:
Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Sweatshops; Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State)
Form and Genre Terms:
Audiovisual materials.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
6000/026: UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Records
CONTAINER LIST
- Carmen Rosales - "UNITE", 1 (Box 1)
  "Tom" :60 Radio -- UN97-08R --- DAT--19 min.
- Carmen Rosales -- UNITE, 1998; 2 (Box 1)
  "Tom" :60 Radio UN97-08R -- 5/5/1998
- UNITE -- "Tom", 1997; 3 (Box 1)
  12/19/1997
- Macy's Rally/Peerless Clothing - 6/17/1996, 4 (Box 1)
  NewsRadio 88/WCBS-AM New York, 6:00 PM
- Jesse Jackson's Message to Chipman-Union for ACTWU, 5 (Box 1)
- Peerless-San Antonio, Texas, 6 (Box 1)
- It's Union Time at Tultex, Let's Stop the Cuts!, 7 (Box 1)
  Vote Union Yes-August 17 and 18
- It's Union Time at Tultex, Let's Stop the Cuts!, 8 (Box 1)
- Breaking the Silence, the Fight for Justice at Peerless, 9 (Box 1)
- It's Union Time at Tultex, Let's Stop the Cuts!, 10 (Box 1)
- It's Union Time at Tultex, Let's Stop the Cuts!, 11 (Box 1)
- United Cloth, "A Question of Dignity", 12 (Box 1)
  AFL-CIO,
- "United Colth-A Question of Dignity, 13 (Box 1)
  AFL-CIO
- Jobs with Justice News Conference, June 22, 1987, 14 (Box 1)
  International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers
- Eyewitness News Segment on Cone Mills Worker Protest, 1992; 15 (Box 1)
  WSOC TV, Ch. 9, Charlotte, North Carolina, 6:00 PM, 5/18/1992
- Tultex Campaign Compilation, 5/23/1995, 16 (Box 1)
  Tultex Campaign Compilation, Tape 1
- Hiring Rosa Martinez; Paying to Lose Our Jobs, 1992; 17 (Box 1)
  60 Minutes-CVS-9/27/1992; Nightline-ABC-9/29, 9/30/1992 -- National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker and Human Rights in Central America
- Breaking the Silence, the Fight for Justice at Peerless, 18 (Box 1)
- Adidas Protest - 9/7/1995, 19 (Box 1)
- Peerless Media Coverage - 1995, 20 (Box 1)
- Breaking the Silence, the Fight for Justice at Peerless, 21 (Box 1)
- Tultex Compilation, Tape 2 - 5/4/1995, 22 (Box 1)
- Tultex Campaign Compilation - 5/23/1995, 23 (Box 1)
- Tultex Campaign Compilation - 5/23/1995, 24 (Box 1)
- Tultex Corporation - Face to Face with John and Chuck - May 1993, 25 (Box 1)
  Paul French and Partners, Inc., Video and Multi-Image Communications
- Cone Mills Worker Protests, 1992; 26 (Box 1)
  1.WFMY, Ch2-5/14/1992; 2.WGHP, Ch8-5/14/1992
- Tultex Compilation [M. Zucker], 27 (Box 1)
- Adidas - Protest - U.S. Open - 9/7/1995, 28 (Box 1)
- Justice for Peerless Workers II, 29 (Box 1)
  English version
- Peerless Demonstration, San Francisco - August 9, 1996, 30 (Box 1)
- Justice for Peerless Workers II, 31 (Box 1)
- Life and Times (Wednesday Edition), 1997; 32 (Box 1)
  #8035 - Guess Jeans/Latino Film Fest/Arts Cal -- 10/8/1997
- Video Report on: Tultex Segment, 1994; 33 (Box 1)
  Aired on: 7/26/1994 -- 4 reports
- Jobs with Justice, 34 (Box 1)
  TV Highlights - June 1987-July 1988
- UNITE!: Stop Sweatshops Campaign - December, 1996, 35 (Box 1)
- Tultex Ratification - Press Conf. and United Mineworker Ad, 36 (Box 1)
- Segment on Cone Mills Worker Rally, 1991; 37 (Box 1)
  WGHP-TV, Ch. 8, High Point, N.C. - 6:00 PM, 1/24/1991
- UNITE - "Tom" :60, 38 (Box 1)
- Carmen Rosales -- UNITE - "Tom" :60 Radio, 1998; 39 (Box 1)
- UNITE - "Tom" :60, 1997; 40 (Box 1)
  UN97-08R - 12/19/1997
- Eyewitness News - 12/3/1987, 1 (Box 2)
  WFSB-TV - Hartford - 6:00 PM; Eyewitness News - 12/3/1987 - WFSB-TV - 11:00 PM
- Unlabeled, 2 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 3 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 4 (Box 2)
- Segments on Union Protest from San Antonio, Texas - 2/11/1993, 5 (Box 2)
  1.KENS; 2.KMOL; 3.KVDA -- Radio-TV Monitoring Service, Inc., 3408 Wisconsin Ave., N.W. Washington, DC
- Unlabeled, 6 (Box 2)
- Jesse Jackson - January 14, 1990, 7 (Box 2)
  Channel 12 TV - N. Augusta, S.C.
- UNITE! - Marshall's Video, 8 (Box 2)
  MASTER -- "Making the Better Best"; The Marshall's Atlanta Story"
- TTB-ACTWU - #16 B, 9 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 10 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 11 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 12 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 13 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 14 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 15 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 16 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 17 (Box 2)
- Gainesville Victory, 18 (Box 2)
  Color/Mono
- Report from WBTV Ch. 3 - Charlotte on Washington, 1987; 19 (Box 2)
  Reeses Bros. Protest - Aired 3/23/1987
- The Beverly Bull, 20 (Box 2)
  4 cuts
- Unlabeled, 21 (Box 2)
- Mine Worker Violence, 22 (Box 2)
- Earle Industries / ACTWU, 23 (Box 2)
- Walmart, 24 (Box 2)
- Walmart, 25 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 26 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 27 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 28 (Box 2)